[Music]
[Applause]
I lost you
I'm a
guess this is your field you going to
burn
it that's your
plan might burn you with
it
why why would you do that
[Music]
we weren't bothering anyone just having
some fun this Field's
mine that fence's
mine you damaged both then you came back
to damage them
more this is my
home if I did this to your home what
would you
do well I'd kill
you that's right
[Music]
the man said if you didn't leave we'd
bury you here and you didn't
leave we keep our word in this
Valley fine we'll leave no it's too late
for that I said we'll
leave I don't want you to
leave I want you to
dig the sun's starting to heat up
disguise all right that's enough
nobody said get
out yeah not much point in
that I have children so do I from what
I've seen yours will be better off
without
you where are you from
California
figures I'm going to leave these holes
just like
this right here in the middle of my
field and if you ever come back again
I'm GNA fill him you
understand thank you thank you is not an
answer repeat what I
say I'm going back to California I'm
going back to California Montana doesn't
want you Montana doesn't want
me I'm to D her coming back I
swear I'm going hold you to that
I don't think we'll be seeing them
again
no want us to fill these
holes you want to put an airport
here yeah I
know what do you want to do about
it I'm not sure
yet don't fill the holes no no rip
sure have the boys take down my tent of
C moving back to the lodge you sure you
want me to do that you might want to go
up there something I'm
sure my summer is over
[Music]